https://www.ltlrider.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
What is a Privacy Policy?
This document is called a Privacy Policy and it tells you how LTL Rider Training use and transfer information we collect from this website.
By using this website you consent to the collection, use and transfer of the information that you provide to us in accordance with the terms of this policy.
We reserve the right to change this policy from time to time at our sole discretion. It is your responsibility to familiarise yourself with this policy regularly to ensure that you are aware of any changes. Your use of this website after a change has been posted will signify your acceptance of the modified privacy policy.
If you do not accept the terms of this policy, you may not use this website.
Information we may collect from you
When you visit or use this website, you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself, including personal details. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site and, if you contact us, we may keep a record of correspondence.
We may also collect information about your usage of this website as you and others browse our website (see our Cookie Policy).
Use of the information we collect
The information you provide to us will be used for several general purposes including: administering business activities; providing information on products and services you have requested and keeping you up to date with our products and services.
You acknowledge and agree that we may contact you by post, telephone or fax as well as by email.
We will retain the personal information provided by you for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purposes listed in this policy.
Disclosure of your information
The information you provide to us will be held by us and may only be accessed by us for the purposes set out in this policy or for other purposes approved by you.
If we sell, assign or transfer the assets of our business, or if our business is sold or merged, or if we enter into a joint venture with another business entity, we reserve the right to sell the databases maintained by the company in connection with this website (including any personal information provided by you).
We may also disclose your personal information to third parties if: we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation; or in order to enforce or apply our terms and conditions and any other agreements with you; or to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
IP addresses and cookies
Similar to other commercial websites, this website utilises a standard technology called ‘cookies’ and web server log files to collect information about how this website is used. A ‘cookie’ is a small piece of information sent from our website to your computer to help us to identify you quickly. The information we collect allows us to monitor website traffic and to personalise content of the website for you. The information we collect is anonymous.
You do not need to accept cookies and may alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies it is possible that some areas of this website will not function as effectively when viewed. Read more on our Cookie Policy.
Security
We employ security measures to protect the information provided by you from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction or damage.
Your rights
You may ask us to make changes to the information provided by you and/or held about you, to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. You may also request that we cease from processing your personal information and that we delete your data from our database or records. Please note that it may be impossible to completely delete your information because of back-ups and records of deletions.
We will only perform the activities outlined above to the extent that such activities will not compromise privacy, security or any other legal interests.
Contact
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to info@ltlrider.com.
